/**
 * @type {{
 *  question: string,
 *  answers: [ string, string ] | [ string, string, string ] | [ string, string, string, string ],
 *  correct: number,
 *  time: number
 * }[] }
 */
export const questions = [
    {
        question: "This class has been a great class",
        answers: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Was there a great Biblical principle each week?",
        answers: [
            " Yes, every week",
            "Never",
            "Sometimes"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Mr Bonner is a faster typer than any of his students",
        answers: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What is Google?",
        answers: [
            "The answer to all of our problems",
            "The most popular search engine in the world", 
            "A scam"
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "Micorsoft word is...",
        answers: [
            "A word processer",
            "A presentation software",
            "A datatool"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "When presenting to a group of people you should..",
        answers: [
            "Look at the ground the whole time",
            "Talk super loud so people hear you",
            "Articulate clearly and engage your audience" 
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Hardware is the physical component of a computer",
        answers: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "If your computer is not preforming the task you want it to, you should..",
        answers: [
            "Throw it on the ground",
            "Buy a new one", 
            "Troubleshoot"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "Troubleshooting is..",
        answers: [
            "A systimatic approach to solving a problem",
            "Hoping for the best when trying to solve a problem",
            "Guessing"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "Photo editing can be a great way to express creativity",
        answers: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "What are the benefits of working in a group?",
        answers: [
            "None",
            "Letting other people do all the work",
            "Finding new ways to look at an issue and learning how to work with people who are different than ourselves "
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "Writting code is super easy",
        answers: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },

    {
        question: "How much time is left in this class?",
        answers: [
            "So much",
            "A respectable amount",
            "Not enough"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    }, 
    {
        question: "Will Savannah be at the beach thinking about how much she misses this class all summer? ",
        answers: [
            "Yes, she will be daydreaming about this class while boating all summer",
            "No, she will be inside writing code all summer"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
]